Manulife iPhones a quick guide
how to redeem
go to the Manulife iPhone's login page
log in using your registered email as
username and input your password
once logged in Click transact
if you own more than one account select
the account you wish to make a
transaction then click Redemption
complete your transaction in three
simple steps
step one
select the font you want to redeem
you can choose either Redemption by
number of units so you input the
percentage to be redeemed or by amount
step two select payment or settlement
method
select the bank and input your account
number with that bank
step 3 review details
once everything is in order click the
tick box if you agree with the terms and
conditions
to complete the transaction you will be
asked to confirm your identity by
entering a one-time passcode or OTP that
will be sent to your registered mobile
number
a confirmation email containing the
summary of transaction will be sent to
you and your Wealth specialist
[Music]
foreign